

MohammadReza Ahmadi Node.is Developer

Get in touch!

Birth Year:

1998

Military Service:

Exemption during education

Mobile:

+989184977873

Email:

mrahmadi7718@gmail.com

Address:

Iran, Tehran

Website:

https://mrezaahmadi.ir

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamad-reza-ahmadi-632039181/

Github:

http://github.com/mohamad-rai

Educational Training

Coding Bootcamp:

Maktab Sharif Coding Bootcamp (Nodejs) 2021 (6 month)

Bachelor of software engineering:

Technical University of Kermanshah 2019-2022

Associate of software engineering:

Technical University of Kermanshah 2016-2018



English



Deutsch

Professional Skills

Node.js

- REST API
- Integration & Unit test
- ~GraphQL
- Socket

Databases

- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Redis
- PostgreSQL

Front

- HTML
- CSS/Bootstrap
- ~Angular

Try to improve my knowledge

- Angular
- TypeScript
- PostgreSQL
- Docker
- Git
- GraphQL

Career Summary

Iran.hr:

Backend developer (nodejs) 2021 - 2022 (9 month)

Iran.hr is a platform to find job and specialist human resource

Feedopedia:

Intern - Backend Developer (nodejs) 2021 (3 month)

Feedopedia was a assistance for bloggers and those who are active in content creation

Uniplato (Legaler):

Backend developer (nodejs) 2022 (6 month)

Uniplato is a platform for managing any kind of online meeting (video and audio). In this platform, users can integrate uni meetings with google calendar, clio, miro and more awesome tools to have best experience in online meetings.

Tic Accelerator:

Member of technical team (wordpress) 2019 - 2021

Emergency Management Center:

Server-side Programmer (php) 2017 - 2018

Ubim:

Server-side Programmer (php) 2018 - 2020

Computer Guild System Org:

Intern (wordpress) 2016 - 2017